FRANKLYN BROOMFIELD

CONTACT

818.730.5094 franklynbroomfield@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/franklynbroomfield-a5492a23/

SKILLS

Project Management Customer Service Team Building Ableton Live Adobe Photoshop

EDUCATION

Howard Community College

2019 - Present Candidate for Graduation Hospitality, Hotel and Convention Management, Entertainment, and Audio-Visual Media Production

Citrus College - 2002

Technical Theater Technologies

Internships - 2023

EventEQ, Columbia, MD Professional Intern

4Wall Productions, Washington, DC Technical Intern

SUMMARY

As an event planner and manager, I seek to use my effective customer service, sales, and communication skills and passion for hospitality to create immersive and positively memorable experiences for stakeholders and their attendees. I seek to use my education and skills to acquire an internship in Event Planning, Hospitality, or Catering Management.

EXPERIENCE

Production Manager, Stage Manager, Technical Director, and Location Manager

2009 - 2018

DIAMOND IN THE RAW FOUNDATION, Los Angeles, CA

- Supported and created the technical infrastructure for audio, video, lights, communication tools, staging, and the set for large-scale productions and Award Shows.
- Collaborated intimately with the production team to provide advice regarding the technical needs of their vision for their shows.
- Arranged, conducted Tech rehearsals, and managed the Assistant Stage Managers.
- Identified venues for the Opening Reception, Safety Seminar and Demonstration Day, Movement Capture, and Award Show. Negotiated and managed all the venue contracts and the events' insurance.

Event Planner and Technical Director

1983 - 2018

PARADISE PRODUCTIONS, Glendale, CA

- Planed all aspects of events ranging from small groups to groups of 10,000+. Included but not limited to housing, catering, media, and A/V. Operated a variety of sound and media equipment.
- Designed audio, video, lighting, and media systems for various venues and events.
- Edited live program content for radio re-broadcasts.
- Conducted seminars for sound and multi-media presentations.